telechargementz.eu 2014-06-25

# GOLEM ® Domain Aftermarket - Privacy Statement

  * Register with our site
  * Subscribe to our newsletter
  * Fill out a form
  * Respond to a survey

We collect only basic information including your:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Mailing address
  * Telephone number

Any information that we collect may be used in one of the following ways:

  * Complete transactions in a timely fashion
  * Provide and accurate invoice
  * To offer a secure domain transferation
  * To protect purchased but un-transferred domains
  * Easily assist you should a problem arise
  * To keep you updated via email (occasionally) about company news, updates, product or service information, etc.

Your information (whether public or private) will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to another company for any reason without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering a purchased product or requested service.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from future emails, detailed unsubscribe instructions are included at the bottom of each email.

We employ the services of Piwik analytics to statistically evaluate the characteristics of our website as well as parked domains. At no time will the identity of individual users be revealed.

We employ a variety of security measures to ensure the safety of your personal information. Our secure server uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. All information received is encrypted into our payment gateway provider's database systems. Information is only accessible by those individuals with special authorization to access said systems. These individuals are required to keep this information strictly confidential.

After you place a transaction, private information such as credit or social security numbers, and financials **will not** be retained by our servers.

Yes. Cookies are small files transferred to your hard drive through your web browser by a site or service provider. When you _allow_ your browser to accept cookies, they are used by your browser to capture and retain certain information

Cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements, and compile aggregate data about site traffic and interaction, so that we can offer improved site experiences in the future.

We may occasionally contract with third-party service providers in order to assist us in better understanding our visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf, except for the purposes of helping us to conduct and improve our business.

We never sell, trade, or transfer your personal information to outside parties. This _does not_ include trusted third parties who assist us in the operation of our website, conducting our business, or providing services to you, as long as those parties agree to keep said information confidential.

We may release your information only when we believe that it is necessary to maintain compliance with the law, enforce site policies, or protect the rights, property, or safety of ourselves and others. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other purposes.

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary steps ensure compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Therefore, we will never distribute your personal information to outside parties without your express consent.

Users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their personal control panel and/or by contacting user support.

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section which establishes the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.golem.eu/en/agb

By using our site, you acknowledge that you consent to our website's privacy policy.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using our contact formular or the following information.

**GOLEM Domain Aftermarket**  
host.at Software GmbH  
Hausergasse 21  
A-9500 Villach  
Carinthia, Austria
